you ever ride a big wheel no you know
what it is what is it it's a big wheel
this is the second proudest moment your
daddy's like this one did you ever take
it the kids didn't ride big well that's
weird to me man that was my best friend
that was my only mode of transportation
for a long time I was white trash when I
outgrew my big wheel and we couldn't
move the seat back in the holes any
further my step back came out with two
pieces of plywood and put a bigger seat
on it I wrote it for two more years you
kid you not until I was 26 at the prom
there you've ever been in rollerskating
all right it's where I met my wife the
roller rink clear the floor clear the
floor plan a fog cleared the floor clear
the floor this next gate is a lady's
choice clear the floor ladies choice
mold man skating around a new addition
cool it now
eating a big dill pickle
drinking a suicide drink a suicide ring
land very nice 21 suicide drink alright
alright
suicide drink
are you lying to my face right now sir
you're a bad liar sir how old are you 22
anywhere me and your mom and dad would
go as kids where they had a fountain
drink machine get your cup and you get
your cup full of ice and instead of
getting one soda in it you get all the
sodas it's called a suicide so we've
called it muddy waters graveyard trash
can either way it tastes like crap but
it's living on the edge that was like
building a bomb in a third grade robbing
a bank you guys let me know about that
bank robbers robbing banks
Bonnie and Clyde Frank and Jesse James
bank robbers back when I actually had to
go to the man who robbed the bank
you had to walk into the back with a gun
show it the strangers tell them getting
up taking all your money I'm gonna do
about it
rob the back kids I've no idea what I'm
talking about they don't leave the house
they rob backs online I'm going in there
I'm getting rid of this Pontiac I'm
gonna get a better car and robbed this
Bank
calling it an ER
robbed the bank man look at me Landon
you will hear me coming
Spurs I'm gonna take a bowling ball take
a rope putting one of the holes the
bowling ball like the rope on fire
rolling in the back like Yosemite Sam
bombers on speed off on a Toyota Corolla
hey everybody Mike's bean burg thanks
for watching that small clip of my
special but now you can watch my entire
special for 99 cents just by clicking
right here or you can watch more clips
by clicking right here or you can
subscribe to the world's largest library
of clean comedy by clicking right here
so either way you got to click something
or I'm gonna sit here with this strange
mustache let's stare through this
computer screen or your TV screen until
you decide you're gonna click something
I got all the time in the world I don't
have a day job so do ahead and click
something already hurry up and do it
click it you know you want to click
something